Narrator: Welcome back.
Congratulations. You made a great choice
in choosing this course to learn about Microservices
and Restful Web Services with Spring Boot and Spring Cloud.
This course has more than 600 plus five star reviews.
At In 28 Minutes, we are focused on creating awesome
learning experiences.
This course guide is the latest
in providing you with a wonderful learning experience.
You can download this hundred plus page course guide
by checking out the resources section of this video.
This course is centered around two key sections,
Restful Web Services with Spring Boot
and Microservices with Spring Cloud.
We also have introduction sections
to Web Services and Microservices.
One of the things which we wanted to focus a lot
at In 28 minutes is helping you become a great programmer
and that means you have very strong fundamentals.
We have two bonus sections on Spring Boot and JPA.
If you are new to Spring Boot or JPA
you can check out these sections in the appendix.
The getting started section in the course guide
would help you identify the recommended versions
and how to install this software for this specific course.
The recommended versions
for this course are Java 8, Eclipse Java EE Oxygen.
We'll be using Spring Boot 2.0.0 Release
and Finchley M8.
The installation video
and the PDF would be helping you to install all these tools.
If you have any problems with the installation
or if you face any problems during the course.
We also have a 50 page troubleshooting guide.
This contains solutions to more
than 200 errors and frequently asked questions.
The course overview section has a link
to the Github Repository of this course.
You'll also find links to the individual folders
for specific sections in the course.
Congratulations, you are joining a set of hundred
thousand learners who are having awesome course experiences
from In 28 Minutes.
We are sure you'll have an awesome experience
with this course.
Let's get started with the first section in the next video.
Until then, bye bye.