Instructor: Welcome back.
Before you jump into section two:
Introduction to Web Services,
I have a big surprise for you.
All the sections of this course work
with the latest version of Spring Boot and Spring Cloud.
Now, you might be wondering,
hey Ranga, how is that a surprise?
The real surprise is that we have now added in
a couple of new sections to this course.
This course is being pursued
by more than a hundred thousand learners
and to thank you for all this success,
we added in a couple of new sections
on Docker and Kubernetes.
After learning to build rest web services
and microservices with Spring Boot and Spring Cloud,
you will also learn to containerize them using Docker
and orchestrate them with Kubernetes in this course.
Are you excited about it?
I'll see you in the next step with web services.